<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Road Quality Audit</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Detecting motion</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About</string>
    <string name="menu_credits">Credits</string>

    <string name="dialog_question">Do you want to start a trip?</string>
    <string name="dialog_positive">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_negative">No</string>
    <string name="not_detecting">Press on the toggle to start your trip</string>
    <string name="uploading">Uploading latest file ....</string>
    <string name="detecting">Sit tight and drive safe! We are detecting potholes</string>
    <string name="menu_login">Login</string>

    <string name="about">
        Why are we doing this?\n\n
        Potholes are a major source of a lot of problems we see on Indian roads. High Traffic,
        slow moving traffic, blocked lanes, injuries and deaths, all of these issues are
        linked to potholes and bad roads in a major way.\n\n
        We at Reap Benefit believe, that all of the biggest problems in our world can be solved using
        technology. This app intends to do just that by putting the power to change our roads in everyone\'s hands.\n\n
        The technology used here is something that is present on all smartphones and this means that anyone can contribute
        to this effort simply by using this app and helping us collect data.\n\n
        Using the data we collect, we will be able to do multiple things\n
        1. Train machine learning models that will help us correctly classify a bump as a pothole or a patch
        of bad road. We will publish these results online.\n
        2. Analyse driver behaviour to detect bad driving habits and helping you correct them.\n
        3. Analyse your car\'s route and give you feedback on how you can get the best out of your car and the route in terms of fuel efficiency
        and time spend on the road.\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="icons_home"><a href="https://icons8.com/web-app/5572/Home">Home icon credits</a></string>
    <string name="icons_settings"><a href="https://icons8.com/web-app/5590/Settings">Settings icon credits</a></string>

    <string name="trips">All your trips</string>
    <string name="low">Lower Value</string>
    <string name="up">Upper Value</string>
    <string name="Thresholds">Thresholds</string>
    <string name="add_car">Please add a car</string>
    <string name="edit_high">Edit High</string>
    <string name="edit_low">Edit Low</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="carname">Car Name</string>
    <string name="carmodel">Car Model</string>
</resources>
